SAMVRUDHI BILAGALI RAVI

<u>samvrudhi.ravi@gmail.com</u> +91-99025-80235 www.linkedin.com/in/samvrudhi-ravi-33805766/

OBJECTIVE

To conceptualize transformative creative campaigns & leverages integrated marketing approaches to build a strong brand and generate business growth.

SUMMARY

Experienced marketing manager with a demonstrated ability of achieving successful B2C (retail) and B2B brand marketing across the apparel, high-tech Audio-Visual, kids furniture, and sports merchandise domains. Marketing skills complemented with strong creative design thinking, and innovative graphic designing.

CORE COMPETENCIES

Marketing strategy	Planning & budgeting	Brand management
Event management	Media/Public relations	Media buying
Digital & social media marketing Adobe Illustrator	Content strategy & development Adobe Photoshop	Print & web collateral Corel Draw
Adobe musuator	Adobe Filotoshop	Colei Diaw

EXPERIENCE

Consultant - Digital marketing | Kids Furniture World & Nothing But Cricket, Bengaluru | Oct 2018-Apr 2019

Marketing Manager | Qubix Technologies, Bengaluru | Feb 2018 to April 2018

Led the marketing function at Qubix. Responsibilities include annual marketing plan creation & execution, brand identity development, creatives & print collateral development, digital/social media management, & event planning.

Asst. Manager - Brand Development | Dickies India, Bengaluru | Feb 2017 to Nov 2017

Strategically developed the brand with extensive brand building activities including leading the trade show team and extensively putting the brand out in verticals of media. Headed the online sales team and helped increase sales while balancing promotions and marketing.

Creative & Marketing Executive | Dickies India, Bengaluru | Dec 2014 to Feb 2017

Developed marketing materials for the then launched brand along with intense social media marketing and assisting for trade show preparation.

E-commerce merchandiser | Raised On Denim, Bengaluru | June 2014 to Nov 2014

Managed online sales, marketing campaigns, inventory management, and backend operations for Raised on Denims' brand, Blue Saint, on Myntra and Jabong. Responsible for research on fashion trends, forecasting, and selection of merchandise for upcoming season collections.

EDUCATION

Bsc, Fashion & Apparel Designing | 2012 | Vogue Institute of Fashion Technology, Bengaluru

Arts-HEPYS | 2009 | Mount Carmel PU College, Bengaluru

ICSE | 2007 | St. Francis Xavier's Girls High School, Bengaluru

OTHER DETAILS

Languages: Kannada, Hindi

Present Address: Sobha Iris Apartment, Sarjapur ORR, Devarabeesanahalli, Bengaluru